Hugo Felipe Riveros Fajardo

Frontend Developer



- Bogotá, Colombia
- 📞 +57 3163042458 👩 hugoriveros18

in Hugo Felipe Riveros Fajardo

30/07/1995

▼ Personal Website

Skills

REACT.JS

TYPESCRIPT

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

HTML

VTEX IO

GRAPHQL

NODE.JS

SASS

NEXT.JS

Canguages

Spanish Native

English

C1 - Advanced

References

Orlando Andrés Suarez Moreno,

Software Development Professional, **Unosquare Colombia** +57 3173417691

Juan Sebastián López Rico, Project Leader, **ITGlobers** +17783188989

Profile

Passionate about software development specialized at the frontend technologies such as React, Typescript, CSS, HTML, VTEX IO, and GraphQL. I am committed to making ideas come true, by designing and developing professional products that stand out for their excellence. I am a person who brings value and ideas to work teams with leadership, commitment and efficiency to achieve the proposed goals.

Education

Frontend Specialization in Web Development, *Platzi* □

01/2022 - present UI development in web applications with HTML, CSS, Typescript and React.

Tourism and Hotel Business Administration,

Externado University of Colombia 2014 - 2020

Experience

Frontend Developer, *ITGlobers* □ 10/2022 – present | Bogota, Colombia Design, plan and implement solutions that guarantee the success of assigned projects, making the necessary translation of the definitions of project design in code. Build the graphical interface of the websites and structure the contents in a semantic way controlling the fonts, templates, design forms, user experience, information maps,

Bilingual Call Center Agent,

accessibility and interactivity.

Teleperformance

03/2021 - 07/2021 | Bogota D.C., Colombia Customer service in Walmart's North American campaign through written and voice channels.